<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Spectrum</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="hint_login_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="hint_login_mobile">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="hint_login_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_login_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="otp_msg">An OTP has been sent to your mobile!</string>
    <string name="rules_msg">Kindly read these rules for question 1</string>
    <string name="online_quiz_dialog">Go to online quiz</string>
    <string name="notificationbase_url">https://xyz</string>
    <string name="head_members">Head Members</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="your_data">You</string>
    <string name="single_events">Single participant</string>
    <string name="multiple_events">Multiple Participant</string>
    <string name="designers">Designers</string>
    <string name="developers">Developers</string>
    <string name="atendee">atendee</string>
    <string name="about_spectrum">\nSpectrum was born from the Idea that the students of IIT-ISM Dhanbad deserve a platform that is truly original from formulation to execution and breaks the Monotonocity of the other fests in college.\n\nThe goal has always been to re-Imagine the concept of a departmental fest and create an immersive experience that leaves the participants with unforgettable moments, proud victories and learned lessons. \n\nSpectrum\'18 is finally here. The 3 days will bring to you 7 shades of enlightenment, 7 shades of wisdom and 7 shades of exhilaration we aim to sweep you off your feet, bewilder you at every step and test you at every shade.\n\nSpectrum\'18 is here. We hope you love it!</string>
    <string name="about_SEE">\nSociety of Electronics Engineers is a society under Department of Electronics Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology (Indian School of Mines) Dhanbad. SEE believes that the students of 21st century are not bound by any limitations to their intellectual capabilities and creativity.\n\nWhat SEE intends to do, is to redefine the potential limits of students in Jharkhand by providing a platform through Spectrum.\n\nTo produce quality electronics engineers with excellent technical skills, leadership, creativity and innovation is the key mission of the society</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
</resources>
